{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Incheon","incorrectAnswers":["Chittagong","Ho Chi Minh City","Yangon"],"question":"Which of these cities is in South Korea?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"C.W. McCall","incorrectAnswers":["Vicki Sue Robinson","Sugarhill Gang","Falco"],"question":"'Convoy' was a one hit wonder in 1975 by which artist?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"\"What’s the most you ever lost on a coin toss?\"","incorrectAnswers":["\"My precious.\"","\"I'll be back.\"","\"Very nice!\""],"question":"Which of these quotes is from the film 'No Country for Old Men'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Elijah Wood","incorrectAnswers":["Tim Roth","Timothy Spall","Hugo Weaving"],"question":"Which actor has featured in films including The Lord of the Rings and Sin City?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Idris Elba","incorrectAnswers":["Peter Dinklage","Josh Brolin","Chadwick Boseman"],"question":"Which actor plays the role of Heimdall in the Marvel Cinematic Universe?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Denmark","incorrectAnswers":["France","The United Kingdom","Mexico"],"question":"From what country did the U.S. buy the Virgin Islands in 1917?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Gorillaz","incorrectAnswers":["Pulp","Spandau Ballet","One Direction"],"question":"Which band was formed by Damon Albarn?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"The 400 Blows","incorrectAnswers":["A Streetcar Named Desire","All About Eve","Pirates of the Caribbean"],"question":"Which film contains the character 'Antoine Doinel'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Haggis ","incorrectAnswers":["Pieds Paquets","Papaitan","Fois Grois"],"question":"Which dish contains offal and oatmeal, and is traditionally boiled in a bag made from the stomach of an animal?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"The Oche","incorrectAnswers":["The Div","The Par","The Sod"],"question":"What Is the Mark Behind Which Dart Player Must Stand Called?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Three vertical bands of black yellow and red.","incorrectAnswers":["Two equal horizontal bands of red and white.","Red field with a yellow sun in the center.","Red with five yellow stars in the top left."],"question":"What does the flag of Belgium look like?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"Victoria","incorrectAnswers":["Mary II","Richard I","William IV"],"question":"Who was the monarch of The United Kingdom during the time period 1837-1901?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows","incorrectAnswers":["The Sea of Monsters","The Battle of the Labyrinth","The Mysterious Island"],"question":"Which piece of written work starts with the line 'The two men appeared out of nowhere, a few yards apart in the narrow, moonlit lane.'?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Red","incorrectAnswers":["Black","Orange","Yellow"],"question":"Which of these colors would you find on the flag of Azerbaijan?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Black Eyed Peas","incorrectAnswers":["MercyMe","Three 6 Mafia","The Velvet Underground"],"question":"Which band includes 'Fergie'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Gelb","incorrectAnswers":["Amarillo","Giallo","Grün"],"question":"What is the German word for 'yellow'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Eating after midnight","incorrectAnswers":["Sunlight","Magnetic fields","Hearing The Macarena"],"question":"What caused the gremlins in the movie Gremlins to become evil?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Dennis Hopper","incorrectAnswers":["Tim Roth","Hugo Weaving","Warwick Davis"],"question":"Which actor has appeared in films including Apocalypse Now and Speed?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"A barren","incorrectAnswers":["A sounder","A leap","A flight"],"question":"What is the word for a group of mules?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Saudi Arabia","incorrectAnswers":["Jordan","Iran","Kuwait"],"question":"Where would you find the city of Riyadh?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"The American War Of Independence","incorrectAnswers":["World War II","The Korean War","The Chinese Civil War"],"question":"In which war was Bunker Hill a major battle?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Cavatelli","incorrectAnswers":["Rotelle","Vermicelli","Pappardelle"],"question":"Which pasta's name means 'to hollow'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"\"Pokémon Theme\" by Jason Paige","incorrectAnswers":["\"Let it Be\" by the Beatles","\"I'm Real (Murder Remix) by Jennifer Lopez and Ja Rule","\"In da Club\" by 50 Cent"],"question":"Which song begins with the lyrics: \"I wanna be the very best...\"?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Nashville","incorrectAnswers":["Memphis","Knoxville","Jackson"],"question":"What is the capital of Tennessee?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Kevin Spacey","incorrectAnswers":["Johnny Depp","Sean Penn","Samuel L. Jackson"],"question":"Which actor played the role of Roger \"Verbal\" Kint in The Usual Suspects?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Haiti","incorrectAnswers":["Jamaica","Saint Kitts and Nevis","The Bahamas"],"question":"Which of these countries borders Dominican Republic?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Frank Herbert","incorrectAnswers":["Ursula K. Le Guin","H. P. Lovecraft","Edgar Rice Burroughs"],"question":"Which author wrote 'Dune novel series'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Shirley Bassey","incorrectAnswers":["Wings","Gladys Knight","Billie Eilish"],"question":"Who performed the theme song to the James Bond film Diamonds Are Forever?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Peter Jackson","incorrectAnswers":["Steven Spielberg","Woody Allen","Martin Scorsese"],"question":"Which director directed The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Jim Carrey","incorrectAnswers":["Gerard Butler","Hugh Jackman","Michael Fassbender"],"question":"Which actor has played roles in films including Batman Forever and The Mask?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"1993","incorrectAnswers":["1973","1953","1933"],"question":"In which year did the European Union (EU) form?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Queen","incorrectAnswers":["Level 42","Deep Purple","Feeder"],"question":"Which British rock band released the song 'Bohemian Rhapsody'?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Nine","incorrectAnswers":["Four","Five","Black"],"question":"In Portuguese, what is the meaning of the word 'nove'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Mali","incorrectAnswers":["Gabon","Algeria","Germany"],"question":"Which country's flag can be described as 'Three equal vertical bands of green, yellow, and red.'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"J. K. Rowling","incorrectAnswers":["Christopher Tolkien","Philip Pullman","C. S. Lewis"],"question":"Which author wrote 'Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows'?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"general_knowledge","correctAnswer":"Mrs Malaprop","incorrectAnswers":["Mrs Uninten","Mrs Misparl","Mrs Anagob"],"question":"Which character invariably misused english words?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"Assassination","incorrectAnswers":["Fell in battle","Suicide","Poisoning"],"question":"In what way did Julius Caesar die?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"A sole survivor tells of the events leading up to a horrific gun battle on a boat.","incorrectAnswers":["A withdrawn boy who communicates with spirits seeks the help of a child psychologist.","Explorers travel through a wormhole in space in an attempt to ensure humanity's survival.","The stepdaughter of a sadistic army officer escapes into an eerie fantasy world."],"question":"What is the plot of the movie The Usual Suspects?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"Kimi Raikkonen","incorrectAnswers":["Michael Schumacher","Max Verstappen","Damon Hill"],"question":"Who Won The Formula One Drivers Championship In 2007?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Read Only Memory","incorrectAnswers":["Random Object Medium","Real Orchestration Mode","Rare Ownership Modifications"],"question":"What does the acronym 'ROM' stand for in computers?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"SpongeBob SquarePants","incorrectAnswers":["Pokémon","The Simpsons","Rugrats"],"question":"Which cartoon theme song begins with the lyrics: \"ARE YE READY, KIDS?\"?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Alice's Adventures in Wonderland","incorrectAnswers":["Charlotte's Web","The Hobbit","Taras Bulba"],"question":"In which book does The Queen of Hearts appear?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Lava","incorrectAnswers":["Ash","Ignea","Pertrite"],"question":"The molten material from a volcano is ________","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Alchemy","incorrectAnswers":["Magic","Aurentalism","Mystic Metallurgy"],"question":"The ancient attempt to transmute base metals into gold was called ________.","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Elias Lönnrot","incorrectAnswers":["Astrid Lindgren","Agatha Christie","Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn"],"question":"Which author wrote 'Kalevala'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"general_knowledge","correctAnswer":"Deadbolt","incorrectAnswers":["Padlock","Combination lock","Digital lock"],"question":"What is the type of lock that has no spring and typically uses a bar that either moves horizontally or vertically?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"81","incorrectAnswers":["14","12","26"],"question":"What is the atomic number for thalium?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"John Tyler","incorrectAnswers":["Martin Van Buren","Franklin D. Roosevelt","Calvin Coolidge"],"question":"Who was the first US vice president to assume the presidency upon the death of a president?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Guns N' Roses","incorrectAnswers":["MercyMe","The Pussycat Dolls","Three 6 Mafia"],"question":"Which American hard rock band released the studio album 'Use Your Illusion I'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"general_knowledge","correctAnswer":"Rip","incorrectAnswers":["Cut","Dry","Fly"],"question":"What 3-letter word can precede cord, current, off, and saw?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"general_knowledge","correctAnswer":"Clarified Butter ","incorrectAnswers":["A type of buffalo, native to India","A style of dance","A cloud formation"],"question":"What Is Ghee?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Pyrite","incorrectAnswers":["Magnetite","Hematite","Chromite"],"question":"What is the name of the type of iron which is sometimes known as \"Fool's gold\"?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Algeria","incorrectAnswers":["Portugal","Andorra","Mali"],"question":"Which of these countries borders Morocco?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"A weary mutant leads a quiet life until a mutant child pursued by scientists comes to him for help.","incorrectAnswers":["Born in the stable next door to Christ, a man spends his life being mistaken for a messiah.","A law enforcement agent pursues four replicants who have returned to Earth to find their creator.","A boy and his little sister struggle to survive in Japan during World War II."],"question":"What is the plot of the movie Logan?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Word origins","incorrectAnswers":["The skull","The age of trees","Dust in the atmosphere and its effects"],"question":"What is Etymology the study of?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Coldplay","incorrectAnswers":["One Direction","Oasis","Led Zeppelin"],"question":"Which band has Chris Martin as its lead vocalist?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Heart of Darkness","incorrectAnswers":["Blindness","The Catcher in the Rye","Howards End"],"question":"Which book contains the character 'Charlie Marlow'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"The Middle East","incorrectAnswers":["Central Asia","Africa","South America"],"question":"Where in the world are peas originally from?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Jacqueline Bisset","incorrectAnswers":["Sophia Loren","Mila Kunis","Hilary Duff"],"question":"Which actress has starred in films including Murder on the Orient Express and Casino Royale?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Ford","incorrectAnswers":["Alfa Romeo","BMW","Austin"],"question":"Which car manufacturer makes the Mustang?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Edgar Allan Poe","incorrectAnswers":["Stephen King","Nathaniel Hawthorne","Mario Puzo"],"question":"Which author wrote 'The Tell-Tale Heart'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"True","incorrectAnswers":["Just a Friend","I'Ve Never Been to Me","Heart And Soul"],"question":"Spandau Ballet had a hit in 1983 with which song?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"Football","incorrectAnswers":["Table tennis","Ice Hockey","Surfing"],"question":"With which sport is Alex Ferguson associated?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"\"Frankly, my dear, I don't give a damn.\"","incorrectAnswers":["\"I'm gonna make him an offer he can't refuse.\"","\"The stuff that dreams are made of.\"","\"You had me at hello.\""],"question":"Which of these quotes is from the film 'Gone with the Wind'?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Alligator pear","incorrectAnswers":["Crocodile fruit","Snake banana","Dragon apple"],"question":"Which of these is a nickname for the avocado?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Sacred texts","incorrectAnswers":["Ancient Egypt","Family Trees","Waves"],"question":"What is Hierographology the study of?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Feijoada","incorrectAnswers":["Poutine","Couscous","Ambuyat"],"question":"Which of these dishes is most associated with Brazil?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"George Lucas","incorrectAnswers":["Steven Spielberg","Woody Allen","Martin Scorsese"],"question":"Which director directed Star Wars?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"Dallas Stars","incorrectAnswers":["Dallas Tigers","Dallas Football","Dallas Predators"],"question":"Which of these is a hockey team based in Dallas?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Conjunctivitis","incorrectAnswers":["Myopia","Cataracts","Glaucoma"],"question":"What is the medical term for the eye condition marked by redness, excessive tearing, and itching?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"Football","incorrectAnswers":["Golf","Tennis","Badminton"],"question":"With which sport is Johan Cruyff associated?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Mark Twain","incorrectAnswers":["Cassandra Clare","Isabel Allende","George R. R. Martin"],"question":"Which author wrote 'A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Tubular pasta","incorrectAnswers":["Ribbon pasta","Soup pasta","Stuffed pasta"],"question":"What type of pasta is garganelli?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"1991","incorrectAnswers":["1983","1987","1995"],"question":"In which year was The Silence of the Lambs released?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Robert E. Howard","incorrectAnswers":["Nathaniel Hawthorne","Henryk Sienkiewicz","Ivan Turgenev"],"question":"Which author wrote 'Conan canonical works'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"1949","incorrectAnswers":["1941","1970","1923"],"question":"In which year did the communists come into to power in Beijing following the Chinese Civil War?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Buenos Aires","incorrectAnswers":["Porto-Novo","São Paulo","Córdoba"],"question":"What is the capital city of Argentina?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Brad Pitt","incorrectAnswers":["Nicholas Cage","John Travolta","Edward Norton"],"question":"In The Movie 'Interview With The Vampire' Who Played The Vampire Being Interviewed?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"William of Ockham","incorrectAnswers":["Denis Diderot","Jean-Paul Sartre","Spinoza"],"question":"Which philosopher famously said 'Entities should not be multiplied unnecessarily'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Weezer","incorrectAnswers":["LMFAO","Static-X","The Black Keys"],"question":"Which alternative rock band from the United States released the studio album 'Pinkerton'?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Gaudi","incorrectAnswers":["Frank Lloyd Wright","Le Corbusier","I.M. Pei"],"question":"Which master of Modernismo architecture designed Casa Mila, an iconic building in Barcelona?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Red Hot Chili Peppers","incorrectAnswers":["The Monkees","Black Flag","Journey"],"question":"Which band includes 'Anthony Kiedis'?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"The House of Mirth","incorrectAnswers":["Blindness","On the Road","Catch-22"],"question":"Which book contains the character 'Lily Bart'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"15th Century","incorrectAnswers":["16th Century","17th Century","18th Century"],"question":"In What Century Were The War Of The Roses Fought?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Stanley Kubrick","incorrectAnswers":["Steven Spielberg","Woody Allen","Martin Scorsese"],"question":"Which director directed 2001: A Space Odyssey?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Tamil","incorrectAnswers":["Berber","Aymara","Portuguese"],"question":"Which of these languages would you find spoken in India?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Greece","incorrectAnswers":["Austria","Norway","Brazil"],"question":"Which country is associated with the drink ouzo?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Tonic Water ","incorrectAnswers":["Dr Pepper","Coca Cola","Soda Water"],"question":"Which familiar carbonated soft drink contains quinine?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Gaston Leroux","incorrectAnswers":["Victor Hugo","Alphonse Daudet","François-René de Chateaubriand"],"question":"Which author wrote 'The Phantom of the Opera'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"general_knowledge","correctAnswer":"92","incorrectAnswers":["90","89","91"],"question":"What is the total number of days in March, April, and May combined?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"1958","incorrectAnswers":["1980","1901","1946"],"question":"What year was NASA founded?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"\"I have always depended on the kindness of strangers.\"","incorrectAnswers":["\"A boy's best friend is his mother.\"","\"Oh what a day. What a lovely day!\"","\"Wait a minute, wait a minute. You ain't heard nothin' yet!\""],"question":"Which of these quotes is from the film 'A Streetcar Named Desire'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"René Descartes","incorrectAnswers":["Baruch Spinoza","Denis Diderot","Jean-Paul Sartre"],"question":"Which philosopher famously said 'One cannot conceive anything so strange and so implausible that it has not already been said by one philosopher or another'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Port","incorrectAnswers":["Soju","Vana Tallinn","Arak"],"question":"Which of these is a popular drink in Portugal?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Cow","incorrectAnswers":["Chicken","Sheep","Salmon"],"question":"From what kind of animal does rennet come from?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Dream Theater","incorrectAnswers":["Jars of Clay","Three 6 Mafia","The Velvet Underground"],"question":"Which American progressive metal band released the studio album 'Awake'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Kilobyte","incorrectAnswers":["Gigabyte","Megabyte","Terabyte"],"question":"What is a unit of computer memory equal to 1024 bytes?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"general_knowledge","correctAnswer":"Lozenge","incorrectAnswers":["Gumdrop","Mint","Candy"],"question":"What is the name of the small candy often used to soothe coughs?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"696,000 km","incorrectAnswers":["6,960 km","69,600 km","6,960,000 km"],"question":"What is the approximate radius of the sun?","difficulty":"hard"},